best practices continue to evolve and
the prudential best hr practices survey
is an opportunity for ugandan employers
to learn and share experiences from one
another to improve outcomes for
customers colleagues and industries my
personal observation
over the years
is that the best teams
are the ones where the leader
team members
employers take joy in the success of
individuals
within that team
there is sufficient evidence
that shows that organizations that
prioritize the well-being of their
employees
realize better outcomes for our
customers
for their customers
higher productivity
and better business growth this
initiative is being held in partnership
with uganda investment authority human
capital international private sector
foundation uganda and the federation of
uganda employers in the last two weeks
we have been discussing the africa
continent of free trade area
it's a 1.3 billion
people market
the best people who are going to perform
in this market
are those who will have best practices
at uganda investment authority the
target that we have been set
by the government is to ensure that we
create
over a million
jobs
in the next
two years
that target is high but it can also be
very easy once the environment is
conducive the insights obtained from the
survey will be analyzed by pwc to give
valuable information to employers and hr
managers on the most compelling trends
under the different thematic areas at
the heart of outstanding human capital
and talent management strategies in 2021
and beyond right now statistics will
tell you that
nearly 75 percent of the workforce
worldwide
is
in that category of millennials and it's
that
for that reason that it's very important
the employer employee proposition
is very meaningful
to our workforce and employees because
employees are our number one asset
following the publication of the results
from the survey
an awards gala will be held to recognize
and appreciate the employers with the
best hr practices participating
organizations will also receive a copy
of the prudential best hr practices of
2021 to help improve their hr practices
abdullah mcconnell ubc news
you